http://www.moore.org/privacy-policy

Careers
Foundation president, Harvey Fineberg, and chairman emeritus and co-founder, Gordon Moore, discuss the Statement of Founders’ Intent with staff.
Privacy Policy
Purpose. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe how the Gordon and Betty Moore Foundation (the “Foundation”, “us”, or “we”) collects, uses and shares information about you through our website located at www.moore.org (collectively referred to herein as the “Site”).  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. If you do not understand any aspects of our Privacy Policy, please feel free to Contact Us at communications@moore.org, 650.213.3000 or 1661 Page Mill Road, Palo Alto, CA, 94304.Scope; Third Party Sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect at and through the Site. Our Site also contains links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by Foundation.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal information.Terms of Use.  Please note that your use of our Site is also subject to our Terms of Use.
Expand All
Our Privacy Policy Explains:
Personal Information That We Collect
You can provide information to us through our Site by going to the Contact Us page and sending us an email at email address provided. We also use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) to collect certain information relating to your use of the Site. Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.  For more information regarding Google Analytics please visit Google's website, and pages that describe Google Analytics, such as www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html.
Cookies.  When you visit our Site we send one or more “cookies” to your computer or other device. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store unique identifiers, user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, tracking user trends and providing relevant advertising to you.
How We Use and Share Your Information
If you provide us information via email, we will use that information to respond to your inquiries or otherwise contact you about the Foundation. We may contact you by email or telephone. We use the website activity information from Google Analytics to maintain and improve our site. Legal Proceedings.  We will share personal information with third party companies, organizations or individuals outside of Foundation if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:
Meet any applicable law, regulation, subpoena, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
Enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations.
Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Foundation, our users, customers or the public as required or permitted by law.
Transfer in the Event of Sale or Change of Control.  If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes or we otherwise transfer assets relating to our business or the Site to a third party, such as by merger, acquisition, bankruptcy proceeding or otherwise, we may transfer or sell your personal information to the new owner. In such a case, unless permitted otherwise by applicable law, your information would remain subject to the promises made in the applicable privacy policy unless you agree differently.
Access to Your Information and Choices
You can visit our Contact Us page or call us at 650-213-3000 with any questions about the information we have about you and how we use it.
Security of Your Information
We use industry standard physical, technical and administrative security measures and safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information.  However, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot guarantee, ensure, or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.  There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.  It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information.  Please note that e-mails and other communications you send to us through our Site are not encrypted, and we strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your consent in accordance with applicable law. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
Questions and How to Contact Us
If you have any questions, concerns, complaints or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or otherwise need to contact us, please Contact Us, email us at communications@moore.org, call us at 650-213-3000 or contact us by U.S. postal mail at the following address.
Gordon and Betty Moore Foundation
1661 Page Mill Road
Palo Alto, CA 94304
